Yuan (Andy) QIAN

Tel: 027 505 0475 / Email: andycodebuilder@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Web Developer with 2+ years of experience in designing and developing user interfaces, testing, and debugging. I have been involved in many projects such as China remote web development, New Zealand local commercial web development. I have got a good team spirit and have been active in communicating with the team. I have been able to plan time reasonably, and I have been skillfully using Front-End development tools in project development, such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React, and relevant technical skills. In the development process of each project, I have made 100% investment and I get the appreciation of the client and project manager.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Intern, Bow Length Limited (Auckland)

11/2020 - 3/2021

Introduction to the project: BOW LENGTH LIMITED is an IT Company in New Zealand, which is focusing on Web/App Development, Media Production, Business VI & Branding Design, IT Talent Scout.

Technical points:

- Development OS: Windows, macOS.
- Development Tools: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Less, Bootstrap, Git.
- Front-End testing tool: Cypress.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

Project Leader of R&D Project, Compucom New Zealand (Auckland) 07/2019 - 07/2020

Introduction to the project: Computer New Zealand is a well-established system integrator for super Micro Computer Inc. in New Zealand.

Description of responsibilities: Apply face classification technology to CCTV to achieve real-time face capture and recognition.

Technical points:

- Development OS: Windows, Ubuntu.
- Collaboration tool: Trello, Microsoft Teams.
- Development Tools: Python, Caffe, TensorFlow.

- Good understanding of Machine Learning.
- Web Developer (work remotely), Meihaofangwuzhizao Ltd (China)
 04/2017 11/2018

Introduction to the project: Meihaofangwu has an S-EPC services Company in China, which develops software on house manufacturing.

Description of responsibilities: Responsible for web page layout, processing, and resolving data requested back from the back end.

Technical points:

"Perfect presentation of page layout based on UI rendering, styling with less compiler."

"Developing projects using jQuery and JavaScript."

"The implementation of the round-robin graph is achieved using the swiper plug-in."

"Rendering pages using the artTemplate template engine."

"Using the Gulp tool to automated build the project."

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Auckland University of Technology
 Bachelor of Computer and Information Science

• ICL Graduate Business School 08/2017-08/2018

Diploma in Computer Science (Level 7)

• ICL Graduate Business School 11/2016-06/2017

Diploma of Information Systems (Level 5)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5 • JavaScript • jQuery

CSS3 • Less • Git

Bootstrap • MATLAB • React

Node.js • Adobe Photoshop • Node.js

rede.je

AJAX • Angular • MongoDB

Vue

LANGUAGE

Webpack

Chinese (Mandarin)

English

Personal Website

https://andy-94.github.io/webpage/